<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Water Power [Basic Bridges/Bridgello (No error warnings)]</name>
	<author>Swenzi</author>
	<targetVersion>0.17.1546</targetVersion>
	<description>
        Sub Mod of the Water Power mod that is built to remove error warnings that result from either Rainbeaus Basic Bridges mod or Bridgello.
        
        Original Mod can be found here (Is compatible with both mods, just spits error warnings in log that do not effect gameplay):
        http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=934418281
        
        Submod requires either Rainbeaus Basic Bridges or Bridgello to be loaded to beforehand to work:
        Basic Bridges:
        http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=920546527
        Bridgello:
        http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=932124891
        
        Adds new power generation buildings that use hydropower.
        
        Additions:
        
        Underwater Power Cable:
        Designed to built underwater, as such is unbuildable on land. Cost: 2 Steel.
        
        Water Turbine:
        Designed to generate power from river tiles. Increased power output during
        rain/thunderstorms. Can only be built in deep moving water tiles.
        
        Tidal Plant:
        Designed to generate from the ocean. Power output can be boosted by up to 300%
        from the use of Tidal Turbines (10 max). Can only be built in shallow ocean
        water tiles. Requires Tidal Power research.
        
        Tidal Turbine:
        Boosts the power output of the tidal plant by 20%, boost can be stacked up to
        10 times. Can only be built in ocean tiles. Requires Tidal Power research.
        
        Lighthouse:
        Misc. building that produces light in a large area, only built on ocean tiles.
        
        Compatability Issues:
        Sub mod should only be compatible with the Basic Bridges Mod or Bridgello Mod.
        Sub mod is compatible with both mods being run at the same time, however xpathing in those mods,
        conflict resulting error message in the dev log that do not effect gameplay.
        
        
        Removed xpathing to prevent error messages from Basic Bridges or Bridgello. As such relies on Basic Bridges or
        Bridgello to perform xpathing beforehand.
        v1.1.0
        -Added new structures
        v1.0.1
        -Underwater Power Cables no longer block path
        v1.0.0
        -Initial Release
</description>
</ModMetaData>
